

PAULINA DOLDER

I am an independent, energetic individual with a growth mindset and a curiosity for new experiences. Motivated and adaptable, I take pride in delivering high-quality results while effectively managing competing priorities. Known for my approachable and enthusiastic personality, I work well in teams and have strong communication and interpersonal skills. My key strengths include being resourceful, organised, and focused on finding practical solutions to any faced challenges.

Contact:

07466166980



paulid4628@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/paulina-dolder-065677251/



162 Lowergate, HD3 4EP

Education:

Royds Hall High School

Paddock, Huddersfield

12 GCSE's ranging from grades: 3-9

- English (Lit and Lang): 6
- Mathematics: 6

Huddersfield New College

Salendine Nook, Huddersfield

- A-Level Geography: Grade
- BTEC National Diploma in Travel and Tourism: D*D*

Code Institute

Remotely, self-led

Full Stack Software Development Diploma Level 4 - until present

Other skills:

- Proficiency in Microsoft Office
- Excellent communication skills, both written and verbal
- Bilingual English and Polish
- Had basic first aid training
- DofE Bronze and Silver Awards

Experience:

Customer Experience Advisor

Santander, Huddersfield September 2023- Present

- Preparing and setting up the branch for daily success by carrying out counter checks, vault counts, and checking that all facilities of the branch are in working order
- Professional greeting of customers and dealing with their range of queries face-to-face as well as over the phone
- Offering a reliable and accurate counter/FOH service by following process and protocols to upkeep to GDPR regulations and our customers' security
- Keeping a neat set of records of daily transactions and making sure the vault and ATM machines add up

Guest Service Host

Cedar Court Hotel, Huddersfield July 2023- Sept 2023

- Greet and meet guests and check them in/out
- Communicate with housekeeping team to ensure that the rooms are available and any extra accommodations are provided per needs of the quests
- Set up conference rooms and accommodate tour guides and their passengers
- Support kitchen and bar staff during busier-than-usual periods or events
- Routine safety checks of the lounge/reception area before the night shift staff took over the premises

Customer Service Representative

Interior Goods Direct, Bradley

Jan 2023- June 2023

- Dealing with customer queries over the phone, email and LiveChat function
- Communicating with all departments of the production, trade, purchasing and marketing teams
- Sales training on how to showcase the product and drive business
- Deep product knowledge training as well as getting to work closely with the company's design team analysing trends and making predictions on which stock to supply
- Responding to stock level changes and being able to offer customers alternatives